{
    "id": "3e2b5466a5944b1dbc7c22f6196215ce",
    "title": "Degrees Of Comparison",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Kochi is .................................. than any other port in Kerala.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "better",
                "best"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "238fce5541764f30953ce55f7481e27a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mount Everest is .................................. peak in the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the high",
                "higher",
                "highest",
                "the highest"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "08f2c2ed17c6413d81188ce81cd0ea7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "No other peak in the world is as .................................... as Mount Everest.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "high",
                "higher",
                "highest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b97dd147957b46fc94e8995c04fd2749"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Amazon is not so ....................................... as the Nile.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "long",
                "longer",
                "longest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eaae96b42f984997a888f658c718cfd7"
        },
        {
            "question": "No other island is as ....................................... as Greenland.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "large",
                "larger",
                "largest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "33f4773c616f4d64aaaa7b61bc720e99"
        },
        {
            "question": "Apples are not as ..................................... as oranges.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cheap",
                "cheaper",
                "cheapest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "40eb3d8b809e4c7f8b065ba021418b26"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mark is ......................................... than James.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as intelligent",
                "more intelligent",
                "most intelligent"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c6b26038be7d4513b85fe3466a08eb16"
        },
        {
            "question": "You eat ........................................ chocolate than I do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "more",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b0c7513a882b4fb1a5e360699c6446c3"
        },
        {
            "question": "No other woman in the country is as ...................................... as her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rich",
                "richer",
                "richest"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fab4a5167dac4ad0bd721878926b4894"
        },
        {
            "question": "Africa is the ....................................... continent in the world.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hot",
                "hotter",
                "hottest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "413f536840834c19b8e5445a5bc55eb8"
        }
    ]
}